♪ Once again
I just can't get it straight ♪
♪ Wonderin'
if wanderin' is my fate ♪
♪ But don't lose hope in me
quite yet ♪
♪ 'Cause help must be
on the way ♪
♪ Any day ♪
♪ From my head to my heart ♪
♪ Can't seem to find a way
They're so far apart ♪
♪ It's not you
It's not your fault ♪
- ( radio off )
- ( sighs )
( growling, shrieking )
- Oh!
- Anchorman: ...our five-day forecast.
Next up, the tree girl
from Elkerton.
Anchorwoman:
After living in a tree for an entire year,
local girl Rianna "Hummingbird"
Holmes is finally coming down.
Unlike the better-known Julia Hill, the
rest of Ms. Holmes' forest was leveled,
though she did manage to
save one giant redwood tree.
- All right!
- Reporter: How are you doing?
I just wanna thank everyone
who sent me food and letters of support,
especially the mentally handicapped child
who sent me this sweet book of poems.
She read my poems.
- Thank you.
- ( reporters shouting )
( panting )
♪ ( "Eye of the Tiger" )
- ( barking )
- ( screaming )
Woman:
Dimples!